http://www.toon-a-day.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
Feel free to read the policy in its entirety but in a nutshell, we never have and never will share your information with others period!
We have designed our website so that you can visit Toonaday without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you have chosen to provide us with personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it is not displayed online and it is not acce s- sible to the general public. Your personal information will be used solely for the purpose of order processing and personalization only. Toonaday strives to have consistent privacy practices for your personal information regardless of the med i- um used to collect the information. Therefore, this privacy policy applies to all online, offline and manually processed personal information.
NOTICE
Toonaday provides this online Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy practices and of your choices about the way your information is collected and used. We take seriously the trust you place in us. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at the bottom of every web page
What we collect
When you place an order with Toonaday, your order information is processed securely through Paypal. We collect your contact information so that we may send you an order confirm a- tion, provide you with information regarding your purchase(s) and for the purpose of delivering your product. We do not share this information with any oth er pa r- ties. Financial information is used for payment processing only and is not retained for any other purpose. Toonaday does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and Toonaday products and services do not target information to children u n- der 13. Toonaday is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents to take an active role in your child ’ s online activities and interests.
How we use the information
Toonaday uses your information to help us understand your needs and interests and provide you with better services. We use your information to help you co m- plete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits and to personalize promotional offers.
Who we share it with
Toonaday Corporation will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable i n- formation to others. Toonaday will not share your personal information with a business partner or any unrelated third-party company unless you give your pe r- mission.
We protect the personal information you share with us. Access to your personal information is limited to authorized personnel.
Toonaday may respond to subpoenas, court order, or legal process. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Toonaday may also collect and share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations i n- volving potential threats to the ph ysical safety of a person, violation of Too n aday ’ s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law
Choice
Toonaday will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ways described above without off ering you a choice. We will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you wish to opt – out of partial or all contact from Toonaday and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. Please contact Toonaday for assistance.
Any Links to third-party web sites on Toonaday are provided solely as a conve n- ience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Toonaday site. Toonaday has not reviewed all of these third-party sites, does not control and is not respo n- sible for any of these sites, the ir content or their privacy policies. Thus, Toonaday does not endorse or make any representations about them or any information, software or other products or materials found there or any results that may be o b- tained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this site you do so entirely at your own risk.
Onward
Transfer The personal information that you provide to Toonaday may be transferred within Toonaday and across state or country boarders. This may be done to consolidate data storage and simplify the management of customer information.
Access & Accuracy
In an effort to keep your personal information accurate, please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address. We have inclu ded contact information for Toonaday to update your information. We may process or store your information in our Toonaday database.
The most effective way to view, update or remove your information is to return to the web page where you originally submitt ed your data and follow the instructions on that web page or send us a message as described in the section below “ Co ntacting us ” . Data access is also available upon request
Security
Toonaday is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the a p- propriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from you online.
IP Addresses
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to a d- minister our web site. It is not stored by us or disseminated to other parties for any reason.
Contact
Information We value your comments and opinions. If you hav e comments or questions about our privacy policy or need help with your privacy choices please contact us at ron@toonaday.com
Home
About
Store
FAQ’s
Contact
Cart
EmailFacebookInstagram
0
